R O B E R T G U M E N Y

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Full Stack Developer with demonstrated experience designing and building web applications utilizing multiple front and back-end technologies. Extremely self-motivated and takes advantage of every opportunity to learn and grow professionaly and personally. Excels at working in a team setting and helping to ensure the success of the organization as a whole.

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT STUDENT

BOISE CODEWORKS | MAR 2020 - JUN 2020

- Utilized partner programming and Scrum practices to design and build full stack applications with up to four teammates
- Completed a number of solo full stack applications utilizing MongoDB, ExpressJS, Vue.js, and Node.js

ACCOUNT MANAGER/LOGISTICS COORDINATOR

ARMSTRONG TRANSPORT GROUP | APR 2017 - MAR 2020

- Trained and supervised junior sales representatives to help them grow their business and bring in additional revenue for the company
- Maintained and grew personal customer base, increased yearly revenue to over \$2 million in under 2 years
- Successfully arranged, scheduled, and tracked over 1,300 shipments annually for customers - primarily in the refrigerated/frozen food industries
- Negotiated contracts and pricing with customers and transportation providers on a weekly basis

INFANTRY TEAM LEADER

UNITED STATES ARMY | JAN 2007 - APR 2011

- Led a team of 3-4 soldiers in both combat and non-combat situations
- Displayed exemplary leadership and decision-making skills in numerous dynamic and stressful environments
- Completed two separate 12-month deployments in support of Operation Iraqi Freedom in 2007-2008 and 2009-2010

SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript
- Vue.js/Bootstrap 4
- ExpressJS/Node.js
- MongoDB

- DotNet Core C#
- WebAPI/HTTP
- SQL
- Agile/Scrum

CONTACT

(973)820-5840

ROBERTGUMENY7@GMAIL.COM HTTPS://ROBERTGUMENY.GITHUB.IO/

EDUCATION

IMMERSIVE FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT BOISE CODEWORKS | 2020 CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION